gohighbrow.com 2019-11-17

# Privacy policy | Highbrow

## **Privacy Policy & Terms of Use**

We understand that you like your privacy, and we always respect and take this seriously. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe how Highbrow Learning Inc. ("Highbrow," "we," "us," or "our") collects, uses, and shares information about you through our website. Please read this policy carefully to understand what we do. If you do not understand any aspects of our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [go@gohighbrow.com](mailto:go@gohighbrow.com).

We collect certain data from you directly, like the information you enter yourself, data about your enrollments in our courses, and data from third-party platforms. Below are some examples to help you better understand the data we collect.

##### **Personal Information**

We collect Personal Information from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you enroll in our courses or contact us with inquiries. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Information, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and agreeing that it may be transferred to the servers of Highbrow.

When you enroll in Highbrow courses and use our website, we collect any data you provide directly, including your email address and courses’ history data. Please note that we don’t collect your full name, so all information we have on you isn’t tied with your full name, hence it is impersonalized.

##### **Analytics**

We use third-party analytics services like Google Analytics on our website. These services use Data Collection Tools to help us analyze your use of our website, including information like the third-party website you arrive from, how often you visit, usage and performance data, and where you’re based. We use this impersonalized data to improve our website and your learning experience.

##### **Online Advertising**

We use third-party advertising services like Facebook, Google’s ad services, and other ad networks and ad servers to deliver advertising about our website on other websites and applications. The ads may be based on things we know about you, like your usage of our website, and things that these ad service providers know about you based on their tracking data. The ads can be based on your recent activity or activity over time and across other sites and services and may be tailored to your interests.

Depending on the types of advertising services we use, they may place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, phone, or other devices to collect data about your use of our website and may access those tracking technologies in order to serve these tailored advertisements to you. To help deliver tailored advertising, we may provide these service providers with a hashed, anonymized version of your email address (in a non-human-readable form).

In operating our website, we may use cookies to help provide additional functionality and analyze our website usage more accurately. If you are interested, your web browser should contain a help section that explains how to receive notifications when you receive a new cookie and how to turn cookies off.

We use your data to do things like deliver our courses, communicate with you, troubleshoot issues, improve and update our website, analyze how people use our website, serve personalized advertising, and whatever else is required by law or necessary for safety and integrity.

We use the data we collect through your use of the Services to:

• Provide the core functionality of our website (e.g., deliver courses to students’ inboxes);

• Monitor your use of our website and improve the user experience;

• Respond to your inquiries;

• Send you information about your progress in courses, new courses, new features, promotions, and newsletters;

• Manage your account preferences;

• Solicit feedback from users;

• Analyze trends and traffic, track purchases, and track usage data;

• Advertise our website on third-party websites and applications;

and for any other purpose for which the information was provided.

##### **MailChimp**

Your email address is currently only shared with our third-party email provider, MailChimp. Your information is shared exclusively for the purpose of delivering our emails, meaning MailChimp is responsible for getting our courses to your inbox.

MailChimp collects your IP address to identify your timezone. They need this information to deliver the lessons on time, i.e., at 7AM your local time.

You can learn more about MailChimp’s privacy policy [here.](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

##### **Paddle**

All Highbrow courses are available only to our members. In order to become a Highbrow member, our website visitors have to purchase Highbrow Membership. 

Our order process is conducted by our online reseller Paddle.com. Paddle.com is the Merchant of Record for all our orders. Paddle provides all customer service inquiries and handles returns.

We don’t have direct access to any of your payment details. All the information that Paddle shares with us is your country, email address, the last four digits of your credit card number, and your transactions history.

You can learn more about Paddle’s privacy policy [here.](https://paddle.com/gdpr)

##### **Other Sites**

Our website may contain links to other websites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or services, and you should review the privacy policy of each such website or service to make sure you are comfortable with it before providing any personal information. For example, all payments for courses are processed through Paddle. As discussed above, we do not receive any of the payment information you provide to Paddle, and all such information is subject to Paddle’s privacy policy.

Highbrow takes reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no internet, email, or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error-free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way.

You have certain rights around the use of your data, including the ability to opt out of our user base. You can update or terminate your account using the Manage Subscription option available in each email you receive from us, and you can also contact us at [go@gohighbrow.com](mailto:go@gohighbrow.com) for individual rights requests about your personal data. Parents who believe we’ve unintentionally collected personal data about their underage child should contact us for help deleting that information.

If you’d like to remove your personal data or delete your account from Highbrow, you may do so by send us an inquiry at [go@gohighbrow.com](mailto:go@gohighbrow.com). We’ll delete all your personal information within 24 hours after we see your request.

Highbrow has the right to update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any material changes to how we handle personal information, we will send you a notice email and/or place a temporary notice on our website.

If you have feedback, comments, or questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us any time at [go@gohighbrow.com](mailto:go@gohighbrow.com). To keep your Personal Information accurate, complete, and current, please contact us with any changes, and we will take reasonable steps to update or correct the Personal Information in our possession that you have previously provided.
